mytelus.com 2011-05-19

# Privacy | TELUS

Although our ability to provide service requires that we collect personal information about our clients, we take measures to ensure the privacy and confidentiality of that information.

Our commitment to safeguarding your privacy is reflected in our TELUS Privacy Code, which governs the behavior of our employees with regard to the collection, use and disclosure of our clients' personal information. We updated our privacy code to reflect the federal privacy legislation that came into effect on January 1, 2001.

We have also developed a TELUS Privacy Commitment to explain why we collect personal information and how we use and protect this information.  In 2008, we updated our Privacy Commitment to provide more detailed information about the purposes for which we collect, use and disclose personal information.  A copy of our Commitment is provided to all of our clients.  You can also access it from this Web site.  The updates are as follows:

  * Under the heading **“why we collect personal information”** , we’ve noted that telephone calls to or from our service representatives may be monitored or recorded for quality assurance purposes.   If you wish an alternative to having your call recorded, please discuss this with your service representative.
  * Under the heading **“when do we disclose personal information?”** , we’ve added two examples.  First, we’ve stated that we may disclose personal information to meet legal or regulatory requirements, such as under a court order or to a government institution if required or authorized by law.  Second, we’ve noted that should we sell a part of our business or merge or amalgamate part or all of our business with another entity, we may need to disclose client information as part of the transaction.  This is normal business practice in any such transaction.  Any such disclosure would be subject to appropriate privacy and security safeguards.
  * Under the heading **“how we protect your personal information”** , we’ve noted that some personal information may be stored and processed in Canada or another country.  In either case, the information is protected with appropriate security safeguards but may be available to government agencies under applicable laws.   For example, our wireless business unit may provide clients with access to music services that are hosted outside Canada.  If you subscribe to those services, your cell phone number may be securely stored in the application provider’s servers outside Canada.   

For more information about your privacy, call us at 1-800-567-0000 or   
write us at [privacy@telus.com](mailto:privacy@telus.com). 

Copyright © 2000-2008 TELUS Corporation. All rights reserved.
